{
  "name": "Large Numbers Recap Excercise",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Write the number 5698 in words",
      "answers": ["FIVE THOUSAND SIX HUNDRED AND NINETY EIGHT"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the number 7896 in words",
      "answers": ["SEVEN THOUSAND EIGHT HUNDRED AND NINETY SIX"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write TWO THOUSAND FOUR HUNDRED AND TEN in number",
      "answers": ["2410"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the largest 4-digit number",
      "answers": ["9999"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is correct?\n(A) 1236 < 1569\n(B) 1236 > 1569",
      "answers": ["A"],
      "keyboard": "options_a_b_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is correct?\n(A) 4456 < 4432\n(B) 4456 > 4432",
      "answers": ["B"],
      "keyboard": "options_a_b_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is correct?\n(A) 3690 + 10 < 3660 - 60\n(B) 3690 + 10 > 3660 - 60",
      "answers": ["B"],
      "keyboard": "options_a_b_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is correct?\n(A) 1723 - 23 < 1700\n(B) 1723 - 23 > 1700\n(C) 1723 - 23 = 1700",
      "answers": ["B"],
      "keyboard": "options_a_b_c_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the predecessor of 4000",
      "answers": ["3999"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the successor of 9990",
      "answers": ["9991"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the number which is one less than the largest 4-digit number",
      "answers": ["9998"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the greatest number using digits 6, 1, 3, and 9",
      "answers": ["9631"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the smallest number using digits 6, 1, 3, and 9",
      "answers": ["1369"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following in standard form.\n9000 + 50 + 7",
      "answers": ["9057"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following in standard form.\n8000 + 600 + 60 + 9",
      "answers": ["8669"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Arrange following in descending order:\n5207, 1708, 1075, 5710, 2181",
      "answers": ["5710,5207,2181,1708,1075"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Arrange following in descending order:\n1234, 4532, 2347, 1325, 4513",
      "answers": ["4532,4513,2347,1325,1234"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Arrange following in ascending order:\n2782, 7822, 2278, 8722, 2872",
      "answers": ["2278,2782,2872,7822,8722"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Arrange following in ascending order:\n5967, 6825, 2345, 3014, 8153",
      "answers": ["2345,3014,5967,6825,8153"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    }
  ]
}